Guide to the Lee Family Papers, 1754-1836
Department of Special Collections
- ORIGINAL LETTERS AND DOCUMENTS
  - LEE, WILLIAM (IV) 1780 - 1796 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - 8. 1788, Oct. 24.Brunswick. Wm. Lee to Vassar. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) finances, account, time to return to England approaching.
    - 9. 1788, Oct. 30.Brunswick. [Wm.] Lee to Barron de Franch. Strasbourg. A.L.S. (copy) in French, finances.
    - 10. 1788, Oct. 31.Brunswick. Wm. Lee to Mr. Hammersley. London. A.L.S. (copy) finances.
    - 11. 1788, Nov. 2.Brunswick. Wm. Lee to J.J. Vassar. A.L.S. (copy) finances.
    - 12. 1789, Jan. 10.Vienna. Wm. Lee to Gregory Bateman. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) financial business, can't get money to get home.
    - 13. 1789, Jan. 10.Vienna. Wm. Lee to Henry Ridder. Brunswick. A.L.S. (copy) financial business.
    - 14. 1789, Jan. 10.Vienna. Wm. Lee to J.J. Vassar. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) financial business, disappointment.
    - 15. 1789, Jan, 31.Vienna. Wm. Lee to J.J. Vassar. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) finances, strained friendship.
    - 16. 1789, Feb. 2.Vienna. Wm. Lee to Henry Ridder. Brunswick. A.L.S. (copy) finances.
    - 17. 1789, Feb. 11.Vienna. Wm. Lee to J.J. Vassar. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) finances, arrested.
    - 18. 1789, June 12.London. Wm. Lee to Hammond. Vienna. A.L.S. (copy) father knows financial situation, slanderous letter, borrowing.
    - 19. 1789, June 16.London. Wm. Lee to Thomas Beach. Vienna. A.L.S. (copy) financial situation.
    - 20. 1789, Sept. 12.Lewes. Wm. Lee to Mr. Rasch. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) another creditor has written to Lee's father, setting out for Chichester.
    - 21. 1790, July 7.Maidstone. Wm. Lee to Maj. P. Butler. N.P. (America?) A.L.S. (copy) Butler's nephew, Strasbourg, bad advice.
    - 22. 1790, Dec. 13.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to N. Collyer. London. A.L.S. (copy) transfer of accounts of company.
    - 23. 1791, Mar. 21.Centerbury. Wm. Lee to Richard Marshall. [Brampton Hinting]. A.L.S. (copy) re: Vassar.
    - 24. 1792, Feb. 9.Thetford. Wm. Lee to Capt. Boyce. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) company accounts.
    - 25. 1792, Aug. 10.London. Wm. Lee to John Fiott. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) missed appointment, financial situation, asks help.
    - 26. 1792, Aug. 14.N.P. Wm. Lee to Mr. Fiott. N.P. A.D.S. torn, account of all debts.
    - 27. 1793, Jan. 7.Barnet. Wm. Lee to John Fiott. Totteridge. A.L.S. business, recruiting party.
    - 28. 1793, Jan. 10.Newport Pagnall. Wm. Lee to [H.] Harcourt. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) financial business.
    - 29. 1793, Oct. 14.Camp at [Lysoing]. [Wm. Lee] to [E. Lee] A.L. frag. auction, joined by Duke of York, Gen. Harcourt gone - promotion to Lt. Gen., servants consumptive.
    - 30. 1793, Dec. 15.St. Mawr. Wm. Lee to [E. Lee] N.P. A.L.S. winter quarters to be at Oudenarde, loss of [Wibbimott?]
    - 31. 1794, May 2.Ghent. Wm. Lee to Hawker. [Ghent]. A.D.S. (copy) horses, regimental business, country in confusion, knife and Mrs. Bartlett, Hannoverians in battle.
    - 32. 1794, May 30.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to Hawker. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) Mrs. Bartlett and knife.
    - 33. 1794, July 18.Duffel. Wm. Lee to Col. Churchill. N.P. A.L.S. report re: court martial and copy of apology.
    - 34. 1795, Mar. 6.London. [Wm. Lee] to Hodson and Hayter. London. extract of letter of Feb. 21 from Rheine, no word of ship which carried Regiments clothing.
    - 35. 1795, Mar. 13.[Apeldorn]. [Wm. Lee] by secretary to Hunter. N.P. L. investigation.
    - 36. 1795, July 5.Lunzen. Wm. Lee to Gen. Harcourt. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) application for leave, Le Marchant, Affleck, Ld. Paget's appointment in Regiment, promotion, St. Leger.
    - 37. 1795, July 13.Lunzen. Wm. Lee to Gen. Harcourt. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) re: letter to Duke of York, St. Leger, Paget, operations against Holland, emigrant cavalry, comte d' [Artois], Ld. Cathcart, Chevalier d'Harcourt.
    - 38 & 39. 1795, Aug. 9.Lunzen. Wm. Lee to Elizabeth Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. and cover, to stay on Continent, Le Vendee, Affleck, leave.
    - 40. 1795, Oct. 23.Camp at Wollersdroff. Wm. Lee to Lt. Col. Beckwith. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) supplies.
    - 41. 1795, Nov. 1.Dowerdon. Wm. Lee to Beckwith. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) Regiment business returns.
    - 42. 1795, Nov. 22.[Malndorff]. Wm. Lee to Lt. Col. Affleck. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) report of remounts to Gen. Dundas.
    - 43a. 1796, Apr. 14.Henley. Wm. Lee to Secretary at War. [London]. A.L.S. (copy) anonymous petition, defense.
    - 43b. 1796, Apr. 21.Newbury. Wm. Lee to [Wm.]. Harcourt. N.P. A.L.S. eve of resigning command of foreign division, promotion, Ld. Paget, outline of career.
    - 44. 1796, Apr. 29.Newbury. Wm. Lee to Collyer. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) Regiment business
    - 45. 1796, Apr. 29.Newbury. Wm. Lee to Wm. Wyndham. [London]. A.L.S. (copy) Regiment business, defense against an accusation.
    - 46. 1796, May 29.Newbury. Wm. Lee to Col. Brownrigg. N.P. A.Df.S. re: Dunn and Rowse, for H.R.H.'s perusal, uniforms and money retained for same, mutinous conduct.
    - 47. 1796, May 30.Hungerford. Wm. Lee. to M. Lewis. [London]. A.L.S. enclosing papers re: prisoners Dunn and Rowse. Enclosures: 48-56.
    - 48. 1796, Feb. 21.Blackheath. Extract of Regiment Orders, not signed, Lee's writing, required uniform. Enclosure of #47.
    - 49. 1796, Feb. 22.Blackheath. Extract of Regiment Orders, subsistence, price of meat, Enclosed in #47.
    - 50. 1796, Feb. 29.Blackheath. Extract of Regiment Orders, every man will be completed in all articles of necessities. Enclosed in #47.
    - 51. 1796, Feb. 26.Blackheath. Extract of Regiment Orders, pay list, Enclosed in #47.
    - 52. 1796, Mar. 11.St. Albans. Extract of Regt. Orders. pay settlement, 20 shillings retained for uniforms. Enclosed in #47.
    - 53. 1796, Mar. 13.St. Albans. Extract of Regt. Orders. pay settlement for Major's troop. Enclosed in #47.
    - 54. 1796, Mar. 16.St. Albans. Extract of Retg. Orders. pay settlement. Enclosed in #47.
    - 55. 1796, May 8.N.P. Robert Rowse. Statement copy by Wm. Lee, confession and transfer. Enclosee in #47.
    - 56. 1796, May 8.N.P. Francis Dunn. Statement copy by Lee, promise to transfer Regt. Enclosed in #47.
    - 57. 1796, June 6.Panton Square. Wm. Lee to Stone. N.P. A.Df.S. Dunn and Rowse, Duke of York, Botany Bay.
    - 58. 1796, June 17.Panton Square. Wm. Lee to Lt. Brown. N.P. A.Df.S. reprimand for conduct.
    - 59. 1796, June 19.Richmond. Wm. Lee to Sir Wm. Fawcett. N.P. A.N.S. McKewin court martial - evidence to be produced, deserter.
    - 60. 1796, Sept. 28.Dorchester. Wm. Lee to Lord Cathcart. N.P. A.Df.S. unable to purchase Lt. Colonelcy., Cathcart to go to Portugal, Lee wants to serve with him.
  - Lee, Wm. (IV) 1797-1800and N.D. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - 1. 1797, Jan. 16.Henley. Wm. Lee to J.J. Vassar. N.P. A.Df.S. settlement of differences, duel?
    - 2. 1797, Feb. 13.Reading. Wm. Lee to Col. Nesbitt. N.P. A.Df.S. wants active service, Hompesch, wants to sell Majority.
    - 3. 1797, Feb. 22.[Henley]. Wm. Lee to Mayor and Gentlemen of Henley. A.Df.S. a court martial.
    - 4. 1797, Mar. 26.Beaconsfield. Wm. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. London. A.L.S. (fragile) Gen. Hompesch, Mr. Clayton, shootingpheasants, house for Capt. Archer.
    - 5. 1797, Mar. 27.Beaconsfield. Wm. Lee to Kershaw. N.P. A.Df.S. Bridger.
    - 6. 1797, Apr. 10.Beaconsfield. Wm. Lee to Wm. Lee Antonie. Colnett. A.L.S. Baron Hompesch, pheasants, game laws, little Marlow house.
    - 7. 1797, Sept. 20.Guildford. Wm. Lee to Mrs. Palmer. High Wycombe. A.Df.S. re: her son, county court case.
    - 8 & 9. 1797, Nov. 27.Guildford. Wm. Lee to Secretary at War. N.P. 2 A.Df.S. re: Pvt. Lynyard - enlistment fraud, additional clause of mutiny act; Quarter Master Robinson, warrants.
    - 10 & 11. 1797.Epitaph proposed for tomb of Sir Wm. Lee Bart. 2 A.Df.S. two versions.
    - 12. 1798, Jan. 5.Uxbridge. Wm. Lee to Mr. Stone. [P_____ Risborough?]. A.L.S. (copy) declines civil appointment.
    - 13. 1798, Feb. 12.London. Wm. Lee to Mr. Wright. Woodford. A.Df.S. finances.
    - 14. 1798, July 11.Guildford. Wm. Lee to Lt. Casey. N.P. A.Df.S. discharges.
    - 15. 1798, Oct. 26.Windsor. Wm. Lee to Woolsey. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) finances, intricate business, affairs, George's finances.
    - 16. 1799, Jan. 8.Windsor. Lee to Miss W_____. N.P. A.Df.S. in French, personal.
    - 17. 1799, Feb. 15.Windsor. Wm. Lee to Col. Affleck. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) re: censure, appointment of N.C.O.s
    - 18. 1799, Feb. 20.Hounslow. Wm. Lee to Col. Dering. N.P. A.Df.S. men given up to another regiment, Sgt. Maj. Mountain, Quarter Master Pickard.
    - 19. 1799, Feb..20.Hounslow. [Wm. Lee] A.D. copy of a postscript given [Lee] by Sgt. Maj. Mountain to add to his answer to Quarter Master Pickard, back pay.
    - 20. 1799, Mar. 7.Windsor. Wm. Lee to Col. Affleck. N.P. A.Df.S. N.C.O.s - selection of.
    - 21. 1799, Mar. 27.Windsor. Wm. Lee. D.S. draft.
    - 22. 1799, Apr. 13.Salisbury. Wm. Lee to the Prince of Wales. N.P. A.Df.S. re: Baron Hompesch, reduction of Hussars, St. Domingo, an appeal.
    - 23. 1799, Apr. 23.Windsor. [Wm.] Lee to Comte de [Roggendorf]. N.P. A.Df.S. in French, Kerr, Finances.
    - 24 & 25. 1799, June 15.N.P. Wm. Lee. 2 D.S. two drafts by George Lee dated Apr. 13and accepted by Wm. Lee.
    - 26. 1799, Aug. 25.London. Wm. Lee to John Rose. Holbern. A.L.S. business with Prickett and Woolsey.
    - 27. 1799, Sept. 2.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to John Rose. Holbern, London. A.L.S. business, Woolsey, Vassars, estate business, mortgages, etc.
    - 28. 1799, Sept. 24.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to J.J. Vassar. A.Df.S. harsh letter re: business, cruel sacrifice of your own brother, asks conference and gives terms.
    - 29. 1799, Oct. 3.Windsor. Wm. Lee to John Rose. London. A.N.S.
    - 30. 1799, Nov. 9.N.P. Wm. Lee to John Rose. London. A.L.S. Greenwaller's writ, injunction, trust deed
    - 31a. 1799, Nov. 12.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to Mr. Mills. N.P. A.L.S. affairs in hands of trustees, Woolsey, business.
    - 31b. 1799, Nov. 14.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to John Rose. London. A.L.S. financial, Woolsey, Prickett, Wright, father's debt, trust deed.
    - 32. 1799, Dec. 11.[N.P. - illegible]. Wm. Lee to John Rose. A.L.S. trust deed, to see Gen. Harcourt.
    - 33. 1799, Dec. 27.N.P. Wm. Lee to John Rose. London. A.L.S. Prickett's bills.
    - 34. 1799.Wm. Lee. Housekeeping Book for Hartwell. Accounts with Ransom, Morland and Co.
    - 35a. 1800, Jan. 16.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to John Rose. London. A.L.S. business.
    - 35b. 1800, Jan.Stevens Hotel. Wm. Lee to John Rose. [London]. A.L.S. Mills.
    - 36. 1800, Feb. 9.Windsor. Wm. Lee to Elizabeth Lee. London. A.L.S. ring, father, servant, tenant.
    - 37. 1800, Mar. 2.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to Elizabeth Lee. London. A.L.S. Capt. Lindsay, passage at change (charge?) of company, delivering her things.
    - 38. 1800, June 18.Pall Mall. [Wm. Lee]. Minutes of Meeting of his Trustees s. Wm. Harcourt and S. Bernard, financial and estate business.
    - 39. 1800, July 18.On board Rockingham. Wm. Lee to Mrs, Harcourt. N.P. A.L.S. bourgoisie, personal, flying fish and pilot fish, crossing equator.
    - 40. 1800, July 18. Rockingham. Wm. Lee to Elizabeth. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. mail, Commodore going to Rio Janeiro, fleet news, journal of one day - shipboard life, meals, passengers, work at Hartwell, soldiers.
    - 41. 1800, July 18. Rockingham. Wm. Lee to George Lee. N.P. A.L.S. floating prison, shore landings, mail, a man will carry a letter overland from Madras to Bombay.
    - 43. 1800, Nov. 28. Rockingham. Wm. Lee to Mr. Lawless. [Rockingham]. A.L.S. (copy) re: letter to Taggart.
    - 44. 1800, Nov. 28. Rockingham. Wm. Lee to Mr. Taggart. [Rockingham]. A.L.S. (copy) altercation between Taggart and O'Reilly, need for discipliae.
    - 45. 1800, Nov. 30. Rockingham. Wm. Lee to Mr. Taggart. [Rockingham.] A.Df.S. Taggart's conduct, will go to court.
    - 46. 1800, Dec. 3. Rockingham. Wm. Lee to Mrs. Dundas. [Rockingham]. A.L.S. (copy) denunciations, to Capt. Butler, case to go to court, Lee's illness.
    - 47. 1800, Dec. 28.Madras. Wm. Lee to Mr. Buchanan. Rockingham. A.L.S. (copy) a quarrel, illness.
    - 48. 1800, Dec. 28.Madras. Wm. Lee to Capt. Butler. Rockingham. A.L.S. (copy) passage fees.
    - 49. N.D.N.P. [Wm. Lee] to [Elizabeth] Desincours. N.P. A.L. in French, advice not followed, circumstances of our union2 Against my parents wishes, I remained in Strasbourg from Sept. 1787 until Mar. 1788 in order to be with you, Mon. de Grasse at Toulouse, Vassar, money arrangements, history of their relationship, in what country is there a law which can force a man to pay the debts of an extravagant mistress accumulated in his absence, Hannam, etc.
    - 50. N.D.Portland Place, [London]. Wm. Lee to Baron Dinsdale. N.P. A.L.S. (copy) illness, financial business, Mr. Archer.
    - 51. N.D., Aug. 18.London. Wm. Lee to John Fiott. [London?]. A.L.S. Gen. approves promotion plans, raising money, present pay as Lt. worth of commissions, Bernard, finances, Prickett.
    - 52. N.D., Sept. 4.London. Wm. Lee to John Fiott. Totteridge near Barnet. A.L.S. business, Bernard.
    - 53. N.D., Nov. 17.London. Wm. Lee to John Fiott. [London?]. A.L.S. to visit Hartwell, business, Harcourt not yet returned from Ireland.
    - 54. N.D.London. Wm. Lee to John Fiott. [London]. A.L.S. Ryder's advice to Lee to tell his father about his business, wants promotion - problems, Bernard.
    - 55. N.D., Nov. 30.Hartwell. Wm. Lee to [Henry] Harcourt. N.P. A.L.S. financial situation, Bernard and Fiott, disappointment.
    - 56. N.D.London. Wm. Lee to Elizabeth. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. farewell, their Majestys, on way to Portsmouth.
    - 57. N.D.N.P. [Wm. Lee] to [Elizabeth Lee]. N.P. A.L. frag. father's ill health, on continent near S. Armand and Condé-Duke's H.Q., Gen. and Mrs. Harcourt at Hermitage, Comte d'Harcourt, Prince Salm's corps.
    - 58. N.D.N.P. Wm. Lee to Elizabeth Lee. Nuneham. A.L.S. mother's health, urn and rest of plate.
    - 59. N.D.N.P. Wm. Lee to [Mollet]. N.P. A.Df.S. leave or AWOL, Lee can't leave until he returns, Carmichael.
    - 60. N.D.N.P. [Wm.] Lee to Madam Noel. N.P. A.L.S. in French, her conduct toward her husband.
    - 61. N.D.London. Wm. Lee to J. Rose. London. A.L.S. business.
    - 62. N.D., Feb. 7.Leicester. Wm. Lee to Mr. Ryder. N.P. A.L.S. Miss Robertt, stay with Prussian army, re: matrimony.
    - 63. N.D.N.P. [Wm. Lee] to Mr. [Tourraux]. Geneva. A.L. (copy) in French, plan for watch he wants made.
    - 64. N.D.N.P. [Wm.] Lee. A.D. Proposal for raising three troops of Hussars.
    - 65. N.D.N.P. [Wm. Lee]. D. Account of bonds, notes, etc. outstanding.
    - 66. N.D.N.P. [Wm. Lee] to [Henry] Harcourt. N.P. A.L. frag. dying friendship, business.
  - LEE'S COMPANY (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - 1. 1790, Nov. 3.Chatham Barracks. Lee's Company. Return of Recruits s. H.E. Fox.
    - 2. 1790, Nov. 13.Chatham Barracks. Lee's Company. Return of Recruits s. H.E. Fox.
    - 3. 1790, Nov. 20.N.P. Lee's Company. Account of Bounty and Subsistence for Recruits. s. George Anderson.
    - 4. 1790, Nov. 24.Chatham Barracks. Lee's Company. Return of Subsistence s. George Williamson.
    - 5. 1790, Nov. 28.N.P. Lee's Company. Account of Subsistence Advanced s. Charles Tudor.
    - 6. 1790, Dec. 3.N.P. Lee's Company. Return of Subsistence.
    - 7. 1790, Dec. 9.N.P. Lee's Company. Account of Ballance due N.C.O. and Private. A.D.S. of William Leason.
    - 8. 1790, Dec. 9.N.P. A.L.S. Lee's Company. Account of Subsistence Received from Sgt. Roy and Bounty due and receipt... A.D.S. of William Leason.
  - LEE'S ESTATE AND TRUST (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - 1. 1800, Feb. 21.N.P. [Lee Trust]. Memo of meeting in Pall Mall s. J. Rose.
    - 2. 1800, Mar. 15.N.P. [Lee Trust]. Memo of meeting with Gen. Harcourt and Mr. Bernard s. J. Rose.
    - 3. 1801, Jan. 20.No. 56 Pall Mall. Lee Estate. D.S. of Wm. Harcourt and S. Bernard. Resolution, Surveyor Davis.
    - 4. 1801, Feb. 28.N.P. [Lee Estate]. Account.
    - 5. 1801, May 9.Pall Mall. Lee Estate. D.S. of Wm. Harcourt, S. Bernard and John Rose. Resolution, sale of lands, Davis, Lord Carrington.
    - 6. 1801, May 21.Lee Estate. D.S. of Wm. Harcourt, S. Bernard and John Rose. Resolution, adjournment, sale of Estate.
    - 7. 1801, Oct. 30.Pall Mall. Lee Estate. D.S. of S. Bernard. Resolution, sale of lands, leases, etc.
    - 8. 1802, Jan. 21.Pall Mall. Lee Estate. D.S. of Wm. Harcourt, S. Bernard and John Rose. Resolution, Poulet's bill, Ransom Morland and Co., Sir George Lee.
    - 9. 1802, Apr. 14.Pall Mall. Lee Estate. D.S. of Wm. Harcourt, S. Bernard and John Rose. payment of accounts.
    - 10. 1802, Arr. 14.N.P. Lee Estate. Accounts not signed.
  - M (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - 1. 1799, Sept. 17.Barrack Office. [Windsor?]. Frederick Mackenzie to Officer Commanding in Barracks at Windsor. A.L.S. forage contracts.
    - 2. 1798, Sept. 26.London. Wm. McNiell to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. A.N.S. trunks completed.
    - 3. 1799, Nov. 2.[London]. Wm. McNiell to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. [A.L.S.]. wants payment, Affleck's credit.
    - 4. 1799, Nov. 16.London.Wm. McNiell to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. bill.
    - 5. 1799, Dec. 2.London. Wm. McNiell to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. bill.
    - 6. 1799, Dec. 16.London. Wm. McNeill to Wm. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. bill.
    - 7. 1799, Dec. 27.London. Wm. McNeill to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. by Barrell. account, etc.
    - 8. 1799, Jan, 3.Lincoln's Inn. Henry Maddock to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. L.S. money due him, Prickett.
    - 9. 1799, Feb. 4.Lincoln's Inn. Henry Maddock to Lt. Col. Lee. Windsor. L.S. re: payment.
    - 10. 1800, Nov.N.P. H. Maddock to Wm. Lee. N.P. Document - Lee's account.
    - 11. 1801, Jan. 21.N.P. Henry Maddock to Mr. Rose. N.P. L.S. financial.
    - 12. 1801, Oct. 2.Lincoln's Inn. Henry Maddock to Mr. Rose. Grays Inn. L.S. financial arrangements.
    - 13. 1792, Aug. [24].N.P. [?] Malleron to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. Estate of John Moore, financial demand.
    - 14. 1795, Mar. 15.London. Theodore [Mannie] to Commanding Officer 16th Lt. Dragoons. N.P. A.L.S. mustering.
    - 15. 1799, Aug. 18.Hartwell. James Margesson to Lt. Col. Lee. near Windsor. A.L.S. work on Hartwell, horses.
    - 16. 1799, Nov. 24.Hartwell. James Margesson to Ltl Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. work on Hartwell, Ford ill, care of horses.
    - 17. 1800, Apr. 6.Hartwell. James Margesson to Wm. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. Mr. Trumper, Bishopstone, gunstocks, plate, list of plate.
    - 18. 1793, Mar. 6.[Ridminster] - Marks to Capt. Lee. Coventry. A.L.S. recruiting.
    - 19. 1795, Dec. 2.Osterholz. G. Martens to Maj. Lee. Hambergen. A.L.S. in French, march instructions.
    - 20. 1795, Dec. 4.Stade. George Martens to [Lee?]. N.P. A.L.S. embarkation instructions.
    - 21. 1795, Dec. 7.Stade. George Martens to Maj. Lee. [Twielen f leth]. A.L.S. in French. Cathcart, march route, Dundas, defrayment.
    - 22. N.D.N.P. _____ Martin to Maj. Lee. Woolwich. Cover w/seal.
    - 23. 1800, Jan. 21.Westminster. Wm. Maxwell to Lt. Col. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. Lee's debts.
    - 24. 1800, Jan. 31.Westminster. Wm. Maxwell to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. payment of bill.
    - 25. N.D., Jan. 15.Grosvenor St. Paul Metheun to unknown. N.P. A.L.S. re: papers and letters concerning last Will and Effects of Sir Paul Metheun, Sir George Lee.
    - 26. 1808, Feb. 14.Colchester. Gen. G. [Metries?] to Secretary at War. War Office. A.L.S. John Field, deserter, in absence of Earl of Chatham.
    - 27. 1795, June 24.Trowbridge. B. Mills to Maj. Lee. on Continent. A.L.S. death of Mills' horse.
    - 28. 1800, Mar. 31.Serjeants Inn. G.R. Minshall to Wm. Lee. N.P. accounts, manuscripts of late Sir George Lee.
    - 29. 1792, May 5.London. J. Money to Lt. Leigh. Norwich. A.L.S. going Paris, Narbonne.
    - 30. 1799, May 29.Lisle St. J. Money to Col. Lee. Hampton Court. A.L.S. in distress, I am... a General, wants to borrow a horse, pension.
    - 31. N.D.Soho. J. Money to Lt. Leigh. Norwich. A.L.S. wants to buy horse.
    - 32. N.D.N.P. J. Money to Capt. Lee c/o Col. Bath. A.L.S. in France, Lee might have been Money's aide-de-camp.
    - 33. 1789, Oct. 3.Pall Mall. John Moore to Wm. Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. spurs, Prince Edward.
    - 34. 1789, Nov. 21.Pall Mall. John Moore to Wm. Lee. Chichester. A.L.S. spurs.
    - 35. 1792, Mar. 6.St. James Street. John Moore to Wm. Lee. Thetford. A.L.S. bill, retired.
    - 36. 1800, Mar. 15.London. Joseph Moore to Wm. Lee. Hartwell. A.L.S. wishes to acquire Lee's walnut wood and gun stocks.
    - 37. 1799, Jan. 3.Judge Adv. General's Office. Charles Morgan to Officer Commanding 16th Lt. Dragoons. N.P. L.S. re: minutes of trial of Dyke at General Court Material in Croydon to be laid before King.
    - 38. N.D.N.P. Sgt. Maj. Mountain to Quarter Master Pickard. N.P. copy of postscript. Pickard's promotion and transfer to new Romney fencibles, back pay.
    - 39. 1790, May 16.No. 29. Queen Anne St. West. G. Murray to Cornet Lee. Epsom. A.L.S. Miss Hart - will not forget Lee, Epsom Races, Drew.
    - 40. 1791, Mar. 13. Triton. Downs. George Murray to Lt. Lee. [N.P.?] A.L.S. wants Lee, Anson and Col. Gardner to visit him on Triton.
    - 41. 1799, June 22.Hounslow Barracks. George Homer Murray to Col. Lee. Windsor. A.L.S. Has written Dr. Jenner for cow pock virus, illnesses.
  - N (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - 1. 1801, Feb. 9.Madras. _____ Narram to Estate of Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.D.S. bill for minister's attendence at funeral.
    - 2. 1799, Mar. 14.[London]. William Neale to Col. Lee. [Windsor]. A.L.S. business.
    - 3. 1799, Mar. 21.[London]. William Neale to Lt. Col. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. business.
    - 4. N.D.[London]. William Neale to Col. Lee. [London]. A.L.S. business.
    - 5. 1795, Dec. 3.Stade. C.O. Nesbitt to [Wm. Lee?]. N.P. A.L.S. embarkation.
    - 6. [1795], Dec. 4.Stade. C.O. Nesbitt to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. march, embarkation instructions.
    - 7a. 1795, Dec. 7.[Stade]. C.O. Nesbitt to Maj. Lee. N.P. A.L.S. detachment of 15th Regt.
    - 7b. 1797, Mar. 4.John Street. C.O. Nesbitt to Maj. Lee. Reading. A.L.S. [Duke of York] could not consent to your disposing of the Majority of the 16th, Gen. Harcourt.
    - 8. N.D., Nov. 11.Shenley. Peter Newcome to Sir [Wm. Lee III]. N.P. A.L.S. delayed in going to Hartwell, friendship.
    - 9. 1799, July 3.Eaton St. Richard North to Lt. Humphrey, and Col. Lee. Windsor Camp. A.L.S. Lee's snuff.
    - 10. 1764, Dec. 17.N.P. N[uneham]. to [Wm. Lee III]. N.P. A.L.S. re: brother's [Harcourt] promotion, Nuneham is not consulted, Lord H., future in Parliament, Miss Poyntz story.
    - 11. 1770, Oct. 23.Nuneham. [Nuneham] to Wm. Lee III. N.P. A.L. Dear Prue, Gen. Evelyn, William ill.
    - 12. N.D.N.P. [Nuneham] to Sir Wm. [Lee III]. N.P. A.L. Dr. Hoare, sister's illness. London (where... the sulphur from the coals corrects the natural humidity of our climate, Dr. Lewes, a London ladies club like Almack.
    - 13. N.D.Leicester House. N[uneham] to Sir Wm. [Lee III]. N.P. A.L.S. thanks for pork, Simon Harcourt safely arrived in Paris, illnesses, flowers.
    - 14. N.D.N.P. [Nuneham] to [Wm. Lee III?]. N.P. A.L. sister's headache, some pictures, latitudinarian.
    - 15. N.D., Dec. 4.Lewes. Nuneham to [Wm. Lee III]. N.P. A.L.S. illnesses, sister, Parliament, neutrality unsupportable, Lord Harcourt, disagreements.
    - 16. N.D.Middleton Park. N[Unheam] to [Wm. Lee III]. N.P. A.L.S. sister's illness, Ld. H.
    - 17. N.D.N.P. [Nuneham] to Wm. [Lee III]. N.P. A.L. Mr. Barnard, raising money, a mortgage, Ld. Southampton, etc.
    - 18. N.D.Nuneham. [Nuneham] to Wm. Lee [III]. N.P. A.L. snow prevents him going to Hartwell.
    - 19. N.D.N.P. [Nuneham] to Wm. [Lee III]. N.P. A.L. sister's illness, pleased with her marriage, floor plan?, sketch on verso.
    - 20. N.D.N.P. [Nuneham] to Wm. Lee III. N.P. A.L. Lady Nuneham, a journey.
    - 21. N.D.N.P. [Nuneham] to [Elizabeth Lee]. N.P. A.L. lameness, pictures and descriptions include two boys heads by Rembrant, Ld. and Lady Vernon, H. Vernon.